

DOB: 10/20/1994

Address:

6 Lukomorye, Vladivostok Primorsky Krai, Russia 690001

Phone:

+7 966 279-03-61

Email: xinli1020@mail.ru

Website: www.xinli.com

- in /xin-li-05007b1a3
- () /Ing50k
- www.xinli.com
- 🐰 /xin-li-43

INTERESTS







TRAVEL CYCLING

GYM

ABOUT ME

XIN LI

Meticulous JavaScript, PHP, Ruby developer with 5 years experience and passion. Possess exceptional critical thinking and problem-solving skills, great technical expertise, and the important ability to perform well independently or in a team setting.

MY SKILLS

JAVASCRIPT N
REACT R
REACT NATIVE L
VUE M

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

RUBY ON RAILS

LARAVEL

MAGENTO 2

EXPERIENCE

2017 to 2020

FULL STACK DEVELOPER FundraisingForACause - Tampa, Florida

- Migration from CS Cart to Magento 2
- Order Management Dashboard (Next.js)
- Ongoing maintenance

2016 to 2018

FULL STACK DEVELOPER Serlex.io - United Kingdom

- 2 iOS native app publication Swift Chef Mart App, Food Supplier App
- Backend development on Magento 2
- AWS EC2 Setup from Scratch.

2018 to 2020

FRONTEND DEVELOPER iMationSoft - Los Angeles, California

- Glatt Mart React Storefront
- Glamour Beauty Center React Storefront
- Fabric & Sewing React Storefront
- Moisha's supermarket React Native app
- am:pm React Native app

2019 to 2020

FULL STACK DEVELOPER Gazri Ecommerce - Egypt

- HiiAuto Magento 2
- RayaPay Portal Laravel + React.js
- Rayashop Magento 1
- Order Management Portal React.js
- Cherry & Berry Migration M1 -> M2

EDUCATION

2011 to 2014

UNIVERSITI KUALA LUMPUR

Master of Computer Applications (M.C.A.)